cisdem.com 2015-06-07

# [OFFICIAL] Cisdem Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Cisdem respects privacy

Cisdem respects your individual privacy and we will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### About cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies can also determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

###  Our companywide commitment to your privacy

This policy covers the Intel Corporate website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Cisdem employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

## Our Award 

#### 

### Cisdem PDFToolkit is my favorite with its nice, clean user interface covering most functions, including merge PDF files, split PDF files, compress PDF files, extract images and text from PDF files. If you're looking for an application that can get most of their PDF-related tasks done without many extras, then check out Cisdem PDFToolkit.
